chloeandisabel.com 2012-11-08

# Privacy Policy | Chloe and Isabel

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to using this Site. By using the Site, you indicate your agreement with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy, do not use this Site. 

Welcome to chloeandisabel.com! chloe and isabel, inc respects the privacy of every individual who visits any of our websites or online areas, and we are committed to protecting the privacy of everyone involved, specially our visitors and our independent Merchandisers. We have created this Policy in order to make you aware of the type of information that we collect, specifically with regards to your rights to and our responsibilities in safeguarding it … responsibilities that we take very seriously. 

##  Visitor Consent 

By entering this website, you are providing information on a voluntary basis and agree to chloe and isabel’s collection and use of this information in accordance with this Policy. 

##  Collected Information 

We collect personally identifiable information (names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc.) when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. You are free to browse any of our public-facing sites without submitting personal information. This information will be used for our business purposes only, and our Policy will continue to cover information we may collect about you during the course of our relationship as well as after the relationship has ended. Outside of fulfilling a specific request, chloe and isabel can only use your information if you give us permission to use it in another manner (such as adding you to one of our mailing lists). We do not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with anyone. chloe and isabel does not intend to collect any personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, age or email address) from persons under the age of 18. 

Personal information you provide to us while creating or updating an account and at checkout is stored in private files on our secure web server. We also use cookies to save product and purchase information from the pages you access or visit so that your shopping cart can be saved each time you visit. Cookies are information that is automatically stored on your computer. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information such as your name, address or any financial information. If you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser preferences to disable them 

##  Secure Shopping 

Orders placed on our site are encrypted using SSL technology in order to provide secure, protected online transactions. In order for SSL security to work, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. We will NEVER ask for sensitive information via email. 

##  Revisions to Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to change or revise this Policy at any time. You should periodically visit this page to determine the current Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our websites, following the posting of 

changes to this Privacy Policy, will signify your acceptance of those changes. Have additional questions? 

If you have questions about your privacy on www.chloeandisabel.com or any of our corresponding sites, please contact our customer service at: [customercare@chloeandisabel.com](mailto:customercare@chloeandisabel.com) .
